A Guide to the Office of the Vice President for Administration Office Administrative Files, 1985-1987
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Vice President for Administration Office Administrative Files 1985-1987
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/1/2.901
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1990 June 28.
Scope and Content
Major subjects in the topical files and committee files of the Vice President for Administration include the Board of Visitors, the budget, the Chamber of Commerce, the Discrimination Complaint Procedures Task Force, the physical plant, the police dept., the President's office, and the University Real Estate Foundation.
Smaller topics of interest include library automation, asbestos litigation, Route 29 and bypass study, WVPT, child care, U.S. State Dept. of Information Technology, space management and the replacement hospital.
Contents List
- Administration, General 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Administration Reserve Account 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Administrative Computing 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  Library Automation, Self-Study Report on Computing
- Advisory Group on Research Facilities 1986 (Box 1)
- Afro-American Affairs Office 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Albemarle Housing Coalition 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- American Heart Association 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Asbestos Litigation 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Associated General Contractors of Virginia 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Athletic Department 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Auditor's Office 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Auxiliary Services 1986-1987 (Box 1)
- Board of Visitors Meeting 1986 Oct 2-3 (Box 1)
- Board of Vistors--Divestment 1987 Mar 17 (Box 1)
- Board of Vistors--January Meeting 1987 Jan (Box 1)
- Board of Vistors--March Meeting 1987 Mar (Box 1)
- Board of Visitors--May Meeting 1987 May (Box 2)
- Budget Office--Operating Budget 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  Budget Addendum (2 folders), General Budget, Capital Budget Planning Guidelines
- Carrs Hill Furniture--Repairs and Payments 1985-1986 (Box 2)
- Cavalier Computers 1986-1987 (Box 2)
- Chamber of Commerce 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  Board of Directors, Business-Education Partnership, Education Committee, Health Care Meeting
- Chamber of Commerce--University as Customer for Minority Businesses 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  Public Relations (2 folders), University as a Customer, University as a Customer for Minority Business Firms
- City of Charlottesville 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  General Files, City-County Hunt Luncheon, City-University Consortium
- Charlottesville-Albemarle County Chamber of Commerce 1985-1986 (Box 3)
- Charlottesville Department of Community Development 1987 (Box 3)
- CIO Agreements 1986-1987 (Box 3)
- City Planning Commission 1987 (Box 3)
- Clinch Valley College 1986-1987 (Box 3)
- Commerce School 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  General Files, Annual Report
- Communication Services 1986-1987 (Box 3)
- Computer Proposals Meeting 1986 (Box 3)
- Conflict of Interest 1986-1987 (Box 3)
- Cost Reduction Incentive Awards Program 1987 (Box 3)
- Council for Adult and Experiential Learning 1987 (Box 3)
- County Planning Commission 1987 (Box 3)
- Crisis Family Day Care 1987 (Box 3)
- Decentralization Meetings 1986-1987 (Box 3)
- Development Office 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Discrimination Complaint Procedures Task Force (2 files) 1985-1987 (Box 4)
- Education, School of 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Employee Communication Council 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Employee Health Service Meeting 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Environmental Health and Safety Office 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Equal Opportunity Programs 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Faculty Forum 1987 Apr 25 (Box 4)
- Fraternities 1979-1987 (Box 4)
- General Services 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Governmental and Legislative Relations 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Health Services Foundation 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Higher Education Strategic Planning Institute 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Historic Grounds 1987 (Box 4)
- Incubator Facility Project 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Institutional Planning and Studies 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Joint Dispatch Center 911 System 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Jordan Hall 1987 (Box 5)
- Lawn Advisory Board--Lawn Improvement Program 1986-1987 (Box 5)
- Legal Advisor's Office 1986-1987 (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous 1986-1987 (Box 5)
- Medical Center 1986-1987 (Box 5)
- Materiel Management 1986-1987 (Box 5)
- Charlottesville-Albemarle Metropolitan Planning Organization 1986-1987 (Box 5)
- Parking and Transportation Services 1986-1987 (Box 5)
- Personnel Administration--Retirement Age Employees 1986-1987 (Box 5)
- Personnel Office 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  General Records, Health Care, Office of Civil Rights, Pay for Performance
- Physical Plant--General (2 files) 1985-1987 (Box 5)
- Physical Plant--Asbestos Removal 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  Centrifuge Research Lab, Classroom Upgrade Program, EDAW Report, Expenditures, Ivy Garden Steps, Riverton Cemeny Company
- Police Department 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  Board of Visitors Meeting, Deputization
- President's Office 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  Administrative Seminar (1986 Aug 28), Assistant to President, Breakfast with O'Neil (1987 Jan 13), Cabell Hall Handicapped Access, Coal Silos
- Condition of Public Facilities 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  Senate Visits, Staff Meeting (1987 Jan 21), 2 folders, Student Retreat (1986 Nov 10)
- Printing and Mail Service 1986-1987 (Box 7)
- Provost Office 1986-1987 (Box 7)
- Purchasing and Accounts Payable System 1986-1987 (Box 7)
- Real Estate 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  General
- Real Estate
  Observatory Mountain Treatment Plant Lease, University Real Estate Foundation (2 folders)
- University Real Estate Foundation Retirement Community 1986-1987 (Box 8)
- Risk Management 1986-1987 (Box 8)
  Risk Management and Real Estate, Rivanna Water, Sewer, and Lease Agreement
- Route 29 and Bypass Study 1986-1987 (Box 8)
- Space Office 1986-1987 (Box 8)
  General, Carruthers Hall Space, Medical Center Space
- Staff Meeting 1987 Feb (Box 8)
- State Department of Information Technology 1986-1987 (Box 8)
  1986 Meeting with Smithers, Ullman, Martin, Prenzel, Johnson
- Student Affairs 1986 (Box 8)
- Student Council 1986-1987 (Box 8)
- Sydney College Visitors 1986-1987 (Box 8)
- University Relations-- Inside UVa1986-1987 (Box 8)
- Urban Land Institute 1986-1987 (Box 8)
- Venable Neighborhood Association 1986-1987 (Box 8)
- Vice President for Business and Finance 1986-1987 (Box 8)
- WINA Antenna--Observatory Hill 1987 (Box 8)
- WPTV [Public Television] Board of Directors 1985-1987 (Box 8)
- WPTV Board of Directors--Shenandoah Valley Educational Television Corporation 1985-1987 (Box 9)
- WTJU Transmission Tower 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- COMMITTEE FILES 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Administrative Committees 1987 (Box 9)
- Advisory Committees 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Arboretum and Landscape Committee 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Architectural Advisory Committee 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Building Committee--Proposed Arts & Sciences Building 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  Cobb Hall Additions, Committee Guidelines, Medical Research Facility Development, Monroe Hall Addition, Student Health Renovation
- Cemetery Committee 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Chapel Committee 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Child Care (2 files) 1985-1987 (Box 9)
  American Express Proposal
- Child Care--Computer Coffee Break Committee 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Computing and Communications Committee 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Drug and Alcohol Abuse and Education Task Force 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Faculty Benefits Committee 1987 (Box 9)
- Graphics Committee 1987 (Box 9)
- Jeffersonian Restoration Advisory Board 1987 (Box 9)
- Master Plan Committee 1986-1987 (Box 9)
- Outstanding Contributions Awards Committee 1987 (Box 10)
- Personal Computers Task Force 1986-1987 (Box 10)
- Replacement Hospital Building Committee 1986-1987 (Box 10)
- Safety and Security Committee 1986-1987 (Box 10)
- Sexual Assault Task Force 1986-1987 (Box 10)
- Space Management 1987 (Box 10)
  Space Management Task Force
- Special Project Committee $10,000.00 1986 (Box 10)
- Vice Presidential Planning Group 1986-1987 (Box 10)